uinterview.com 2019-06-25

# Privacy - uInterview

Use of this Web site constitutes acceptance of our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

**Information Collected**

We collect personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, e-mail address) when you subscribe to our newsletters, make a post or register for any portion of our services. Optional information such as your age, gender, interests and hobbies may also be requested. We also collect non-personally identifiable information (such as your IP address or domain, or about your site usage) for purposes of site administration or improvement, and to compile aggregate information about usage of this site.

**Use of Information**

Uinterview collects personal information in order to provide guests with a personalized online experience and to provide our advertisers with a way to reach the right audience. We may use the information you provide to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs, services, companies or events that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also use the information to communicate with you, such as send you our newsletter, notify you about events or promotions, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs. On a confidential basis, Uinterview may also share personal information with our corporate affiliates or consultants or with third parties that perform a particular service on our behalf (such as marketing, printing, mailing, credit card processing, or general site administration), and may also share aggregate information with third parties for advertising and promotional purposes. We may also disclose personal information in response to a legal process, such as a request by law enforcement, a court order or subpoena, or to protect the integrity of our site if we believe that a guest has committed unlawful or otherwise harmful acts.

**Use of IP Address**

An IP address (Internet Protocol address) is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you log on to the Web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address, so when a guest requests pages from our site, our servers log the guest’s IP address. The IP addresses of our guests are collected only for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers, our corporate affiliates or consultants, or with third parties that perform a particular service on our behalf. We do not combine IP addresses with any personally identifiable information, nor do we compile any session activity reports by IP address.

**Third-Party Use**

When registering for our newsletter on this site, Uinterview provides visitors with an opportunity to receive offers from advertisers and other companies who have services, products, and offers that we think might be of interest to you. If you do not at that time indicate a preference not to receive such offers, Uinterview will from time to time provide your contact information to these entities so that they may send you these offers. If you do not decline to receive such offers at the time you provide your information or if you change your mind and no longer want us to share your contact information with others, send an e-mail to [editor@uinterview.com](mailto:publisher@uinterview.com) as described in the Privacy Options section below.

If you provide information to Uinterview in connection with a promotion with a third-party entity or web site linked to this site (such as the purchase of other products), the information you provide will be used for the purpose for which you provided the information and will be shared with that third-party entity. These third-party entities may obtain personally identifiable information that guests voluntarily submit to participate in the promotion. Uinterview has no control over the third-party entities’ use of this information. Your personal information may also be used for other purposes that may be disclosed at the time your information is requested.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Cookies**

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website or other websites.  
Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/#!/).)  
If you have not opted out of third-party ad serving, the cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on your site, which should also be disclosed in your privacy policy in the following manner:

– Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site.  
– Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites.  
– Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendors’ uses of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.info.  
– Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we’re unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative for guidance on drafting a privacy policy. For additional details regarding cookie consent notices, please refer to cookiechoices.org.

**Security**

No transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, Uinterview cannot absolutely guarantee the security of the any information you provide to us.

Agents and contractors of Uinterview who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Uinterview.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personally identifiable information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail. By using this Web site, you consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.

Any unauthorized access to or use of the Uinterview Web site or information collected and maintained by Uinterview Web site should be immediately brought to the attention of Uinterview at the customer service e-mail address below.

**Privacy Options**

You have the right to “opt-out” of certain Uinterview uses of your personal information. At the time you are requested to provide personal information on this site, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to, receive e-mail offers from Uinterview or have your personal information shared with other companies. You may also make this request by sending an e-mail to [editor@uinterview.com](mailto:publisher@uinterview.com). In this e-mail please say whether you would like to opt-out of receiving e-mail offers from Uinterview and/or having your personal information shared with other companies. Also, a request to have us stop sharing your personal information with other companies will only apply as of the date of the request, and Uinterview will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from companies that received your personal information prior to your request. In these cases, please contact that company directly.

If you prefer not to receive traditional mail or other off-line promotions from Uinterview, please send us an e-mail at [editor@uinterview.com](mailto:publisher@uinterview.com). Uinterview will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt-out of these unrelated uses.

**Note to Parents**

Children should always ask permission before providing any personal information online. No information should be submitted to or posted on this site by any minor (a guest under 18 years of age) without the consent of a parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, we do not knowingly provide any personally identifiable information about minors, regardless of its source, to third parties, nor is this information knowingly used by Uinterview for any marketing or promotional purposes.

**Policy Modification**

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, without notice to users of this site. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Web site.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about any aspect of this Privacy Policy or its implementation please contact us via e-mail at [editor@uinterview.com](mailto:publisher@uinterview.com)
